[distant sirens wailing]
[officer 1] You fucker, hold still!
Stay still, punk!
[officer 2] You're under arrest
for murder.
You have the right to an attorney.
[man 1] Let go of me!
[whistle blowing]
[man 1 yelling indistinctly]
- Let go of me!
- [officer 2] We need backup.
[whooshing]
[man 1] Fuck you!
[officer 3] Grab the kid.
[man 2 panting]
[somber music playing]
- My mom and dad…
- [man 1 yelling indistinctly]
My brother…
You have to save them.
[man 1 screams]
- [typewriter keys clacking]
- [phone ringing]
[officer 4] Thanks.
Get a fucking move on.
[officer 5] If you'd like to be a witness,
we could arrange that too.
Hey, everybody ready?
Cho, how's the statement going?
Yeah, we're almost there.
[officer 6] Why are you still wearing
your bloody clothes?
Reporters are everywhere.
We all have to be ready, understood?
[officers] Yes, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
Listen,
I'll… take you to the hospital
as soon as I'm done.
All you have to do is sit tight, hmm?
Okay.
[officer 7] Okay, great.
And what time did this happen?
[uneasy music playing]
[tense music playing]
[prisoner] Detective Cho!
The kid has a gun!
No! Don't!
Don't do it!
Nobody move!
[breathing shakily]
Do…
- [prisoner] Hey.
- [Cho] Lee Do!
Look at me, okay? Huh?
Come on.
[Cho] Shut your fucking mouth!
[prisoner laughs] Shoot me.
- What are you waiting for?
- [Cho] Lee Do!
[music fades]
Go ahead.
[sobs, screams]
[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
[officer] Shooting at Yeongseong Gosiwon.
All units in the area,
report to the scene immediately.
I repeat, shooting at Yeongseong Gosiwon.
All units in the area…
[people screaming]
[automatic gunfire]
[man 1 screams]
[man 2 grunting]
What's going on? Are you okay?!
[gunfire]
[chuckling]
[officer 1] Officer Kim! Officer Kim!
[man 3] Get out of here, man! Oh God!
- Where is the shooter?
- He's inside.
[officer 1] Okay, let's go!
Spread out!
[music fades]
My life…
[thunder rumbling]
[somber music playing]
…is finally ending on a high note.
[officer 2] You there.
Drop your weapon!
Finally…
[officer 2] Don't move!
You know, these guns are
surprisingly easy to use.
So easy.
[officer 2] Drop the gun
and put your hands up!
I heard the first rounds you guys shoot…
[music stops]
…are always the ones filled with blanks.
- What?
- [gun clicks]
[dramatic music playing]
[officer 3 grunts]
[siren wailing]
Get down!
Get out! Get out!
Why save any of you?
You're nothing but trash.
[officer] All units! An officer was shot!
The suspect is
currently armed with a machine gun.
- [officer grunting]
- [Do] You okay?
- Yes.
- And the people inside?
They're all too scared
to come out right now.
[automatic gunfire]
[Jeong-tae] Come out, you fuckers!
Just wait here.
- What? Officer Lee!
- [Jeong-tae] Think I won't find you?
- Huh?
- [automatic gunfire]
[woman screams, whimpers]
[Jeong-tae] I told you.
You shouldn't have ignored
everything I said.
This would have never happened
if you'd all been more considerate.
- [automatic gunfire]
- [glass shattering]
All of you people drove me to this!
Did I ask for something unreasonable?!
- [automatic gunfire]
- [woman whimpering]
[woman screams]
All you needed to do
was not touch other people's food.
- Not talk loudly in shared spaces!
- [automatic gunfire]
Not talk loudly in shared spaces.
Is that so hard?
There's no hope here.
[exhales]
[Jeong-tae] It doesn't exist
in this place.
Your lives are drowning, just like mine.
I'll set you all free
by killing each and every one of you.
[tense music playing]
I'll find you all,
no matter how well you hide.
[breathing shakily]
[man 4 exclaims in alarm]
[man 4] Please spare me!
[automatic gunfire]
Listen to me carefully.
The shooter has an M4.
He's fired three rounds
and is left with 27.
- [man screams]
- [automatic gunfire]
[officers exclaim in panic]
Twenty-four now.
I'll make him waste his ammo
while you guys rescue the others.
Officer Lee, maybe there's another way?
Don't worry about me. We have to save
as many of them as possible.
[music fades]
[uneasy music playing]
What is this?
[lights plinking]
[tense music playing]
[panting]
[yelling furiously]
[gun clicks]
[magazine clatters]
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
Damn you!
Hey!
Come on. Come on!
[Jeong-u] This way.
[music fades]
[rapid footsteps]
[Jeong-tae] Motherfucker!
You're not allowed to save anyone!
[dramatic music resumes]
[groans]
Get in there! Hurry!
[music subsides]
I told you…
[inspirational music playing]
[yells] Oh!
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you.
- Good work, officers.
- It's my duty.
[officer 2] We need traffic control.
- [officer 1] No photos!
- [officer 2] Make your way there ASAP.
[man 1] Chief Yoon! Over here!
- [woman 1] Chief Yoon!
- [woman 2] Chief Yoon!
- [reporters shouting questions]
- [siren wailing]
[exhales deeply]
Security cameras?
Well, they'll be difficult to obtain
since the computer was destroyed, sir.
Any witnesses?
No one is ready to make a statement,
so it'll take some time.
[sighs] What a disaster.
- [officer 1] Can we check the markings?
- [officer 2] On it, sir.
[cameras clicking]
[officer 3] We need to secure Unit 308
as well!
[intriguing music playing]
[officer 4] Finish up here.
- And itemize everything.
- [officer 5] Yes, sir.
[bed creaks]
[hollow thuds]
[sighs]
I remember this.
Stayed in a place just like it
when I was studying to get into the force.
Trapped here all by yourself.
[sighs] At times,
I felt like I was losing my mind.
[suspenseful music playing]
Back in your day,
did you sleep on plywood?
No. I mean, who would do that?
It's not a coffin.
[Jeong-u gasps]
[Jeong-u] My God.
Officer Jeong.
Have you ever seen anything like this?
- [music fades]
- Chief Yoon! More guns have been found.
What?!
[Seo] They've all been itemized.
You can check them yourself, sir.
They're all automatic…
Call the military
and ask them to send a gun expert.
Yes, Chief.
Hey, we need someone here who knows…
- Listen.
- [inhales deeply]
[Yoon] Who's this?
I told you to get an expert in here.
Uh… Officer Lee, uh, was in the military
before he became a police officer, sir.
[Yoon] Then he can explain what he knows
before a real expert gets here.
[Do sighs]
What the hell is he doing?
If you don't know what you're doing,
just stay out of it.
All right, sir.
Allow me to explain.
[intriguing music playing]
[whooshing]
[intriguing music continues]
[music fades]
Let me give you a rundown.
This is the XM177,
used by the US special ops
during the Vietnam War.
And this is the AK-47,
a 7.62-millimeter Kalashnikov,
produced by the Soviet Union.
And this is, uh, the German MP5,
first introduced back in 1964,
iconically used for counterterrorism
across the world.
And finally, the MK MOD 1,
a special warfare standard-issue rifle.
It's modified and modernized,
widely used by US Special Forces.
So you're saying that all of these guns,
that were used in past conflicts
and wars around the world,
were discovered here in Korea?
That true? You believe that?
Yes.
There's something else.
You remember the bullets
found at that suicide scene?
The ones that we found
in the ceiling of that house?
- [Do] Yes.
- We're still looking into that. Why?
The bullets found on the scene
fit the guns we have here.
They're all compatible.
[unsettling music playing]
In my opinion,
the two cases are strongly related.
Okay.
We're onto something important.
No one can breathe a word of this.
No journalists.
- Yes, sir.
[Yoon] Let's wrap this up.
[sighs]
[man 1] Man, I'm starving.
Fuck's sakes, when's he coming out?
[man 1] Can I have some?
- [man] Shocking news in Gyeongin gosiwon.
- Holy shit, take a look at this.
Police have arrested the shooter.
A student resident of the gosiwon
was caught on the scene…
MASS SHOOTING AT GOSIWON
- He is presently in police custody.
- Hmm. Are we living in the US or what?
Fuck, I have a bad feeling
about this shit.
- I really do.
- [man 2] Don't be so dramatic.
[man 3] Oh shit.
- [man 4] Shooting people in the back?
- [man 3] Look at this. It's fucking crazy.
- Hey, go see what's going on.
- Yes, sir.
- [clattering]
- [glass shatters]
[man 5] Stand up, you bastard!
Let go, you fucking goons!
You'll pay for this!
Shut the fuck up!
I know who you all are!
Yong-gu, you fucking bastard!
For God's sake!
Stop this! Hey!
Please stop this madness!
[whimpering]
I know you still have some humanity!
Please! Let's talk. Huh?
Let's go inside, a… and we can
both have a drink, and we can--
Oh, drinking is the worst.
You should really give that up.
What do you want?
Things would be different if you'd
handed over the business I asked for.
We can still negotiate!
[groans]
You fucking bastards!
Let go of me! God dammit!
Damn you!
[whimpering]
Oh! Good work, everyone.
- Go home now.
- [man 5] Yes, sir.
- Yong-gu.
- Sir.
Once I sort this out,
the business is yours.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
And don't forget to take care of this guy.
- [men] Yes, sir.
- I curse you, you son of a bitch!
- You're a fucking traitor!
- [chuckling]
Motherfucker!
- Get this off of me, you bastards!
- [chuckling]
- [engine starts]
- [captive groaning]
Get this off of me!
- [men grunting]
Okay, it's time to get ready.
- [captive groaning]
- Come on!
[man 3] Game on.
[man 4] Let's go.
Here we go, yo!
- Fuck yeah!
- [man 3] All right.
- [man grunts]
- On three. One two…
[men grunt]
- Ah, this job is a pain in the ass.
- Hey, gofers.
Don't forget your mops and brooms.
It's pretty messy in there today.
[Yong-gu chuckling]
Oh, shut your mouth, you asshole.
You take your sweet-ass time,
and then tell us to hurry up?
Don't stress about it.
[tuts] Fucking losers.
- Yeah.
- Don't you look at me with your ugly face!
[slurps]
[Seo] Are you out of your damn mind?
Who ordered this for him?
This isn't a restaurant, huh?
[officer 1] He said he'd cooperate
if we ordered food.
- Get that out. Captain Joo is on his way.
- Sorry, sir.
[Joo sighs]
You.
What's your deal?
Where'd you get that gun?
The gun?
[sighs]
I told you.
I'll only talk to that guy.
We meet again.
Why did you ask to see me?
I wasn't really aware of it
in the heat of the moment,
but when you grabbed my face
and put it into the wall… Bang!
…all I could think of was…
this guy's the real deal.
He works on a whole other level.
Someone I can respect.
[laughs manically]
[Joo scoffs]
Do you hear the same shit I'm hearing?
I'm happy to talk
as long as it's you asking the questions.
[Joo] Turn it up.
[volume control turns]
Where did you get the gun?
It was couriered to me.
And who sent it?
Don't know.
I don't know how much longer
I can listen to this shit.
Why would a stranger send you a package
with a gun in it by courier? The truth.
Why it showed up, I don't really know.
It's probably
because I desperately wanted it.
Shouldn't this guy be medicated?
[sighs] I don't know.
None of this seems real.
Jeong-tae.
- This isn't a time for joking around.
- [tense music playing]
If you knew anything about me,
you'd know I take things very seriously.
What's your history with guns?
Far, near, middle.
Far, near, middle. [laughs]
Like the military.
[tense music continues]
Were the guns hidden under your bed
also couriered to you?
[sighs deeply]
You see, that's the weird part.
I definitely said… I definitely said
that I would just like
one decent one for protection,
so I don't really know why
they sent me so many.
Just thinking about it makes me angry.
[sighs] Jeong-tae.
Do you know how many people died
because of you?
If you feel sorry at all
about what you've done to them,
you should answer my questions truthfully.
Fuck them all.
[music intensifies]
Do you think those bastards felt sorry
about what they did?
Those assholes who had no respect
for the law, rules, or even common sense!
Fuck them.
Whatever your reason,
you can't justify shooting so many people.
Have you been listening
to what I said at all?!
Just like you guys catch criminals
and put them away,
I did the same thing
to a bunch of scumbags.
Do you know how many people I saved?
By killing off just 20 of those scumbags,
I've made hundreds of people safe.
So why… why don't you ask me about that?!
[breathing deeply]
What I did is no different
than what you do.
I did exactly what the police failed to.
You think we're alike?
You don't think we are?
Will you at least admit that I'm a…
a champion of justice?
[tense music continues]
[Jeong-tae sighs]
There are… more guns out there.
[Do] What do you mean?
There are more people out there with guns.
Do you know this for sure?
[Yoon] What's he doing?
I know because I saw it.
Saw what?
[sighs]
All the people who want guns.
And who are these people?
[music fades]
Isn't that your job to find out?
[Yoon] That bastard is acting stupid
and playing us for a bunch of fools.
Given his psychiatric history,
he's just looking to plead insanity.
We should still look into it.
- It could get even worse if we do nothing.
- [Yoon] Look into what?
How does that even make sense?
A gun? In the mail?
[Seo] Hold on.
You don't actually believe
what he said, do you?
If he had those guns couriered to him,
how did he pay for them?
He only has 530,000 won in his account.
Nothing suspicious,
not even a credit card.
So… who would send guns,
to a guy like that just for free?
That's where we should start.
Who's doing this and the reason why.
[reporters clamoring]
[female reporter] What was your motive?
[male reporter 1]
How many people are dead?
How many in the hospital?
[male reporter 2] Any comment?
- [clamoring continues]
- Excuse me. Captain Joo.
I just have one question.
- Don't bother me, kid. I'm busy.
- You heard the man.
These are guns. There are more, right?
This is an ongoing investigation,
so I can't comment at the moment.
Why are you being so tight-lipped?
I know what I saw. There are more guns.
- Smuggled? Or handmade? You tell me.
- Hey, let it go!
I'll write something based on this photo.
You're a reporter, for God's sake.
Write articles based on fact, not fiction.
- You should know better than that.
- [engine starts]
If you don't tell us the facts,
I'm forced to make it up!
[siren wailing]
Captain!
[woman sighs]
Oh my!
Today's rice is perfect. Hmm?
I was worried,
because the forecast said
it was going to rain yesterday,
but it was actually very sunny.
I didn't feel the cold at all.
[somber music playing]
Eat up, son.
And I'm gonna do my best for you today.
Bye, love. You have a good day, okay?
Hmm. [inhales deeply]
LISTEN TO MY DEAD SON'S MESSAGE!
[landlady] Well, word spread
that someone died here,
so no one wants to rent it now.
I'm so angry this had to happen.
- I see.
- What are you looking for in there anyway?
- [groans in disgust]
- Uh, we just wanted to check something.
So you say no one came by to visit,
or no deliveries at all?
Deliveries?
I don't think he had
any friends or family.
Thank you, ma'am.
[sighs]
[Jeong-u] Officer Lee?
May I ask what you're looking at?
The gosiwon over there.
Do you think the shooter saying
there were more guns out there
was telling the truth?
I really hope
he was just making the whole thing up.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah. I hope so too.
There's no way that guns
should be so easy to get.
- [boy panting]
- [indistinct chatter]
[boy 1] Really?
Are you fucking kidding me?
[boy 1 sighs]
Not a single one of these
is worth selling for shit.
Do you hear what I'm telling you?
Look. [sighs]
These turn you on?
How long are you gonna take
worthless photos like these, huh?
It's about fucking time!
Your friend here is
having trouble breathing.
- You better hurry, fat-ass!
- [boy 3] Come on!
Hurry your ass. He's gonna die, man.
- [choking]
- You wanna have that on your conscience?
Run, run, run, run!
Faster! Faster, you prick! Run!
What are you doing?
[boy 4 groans]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
Take it.
Here. That's everything.
Hey.
[somber music playing]
[boy 4 panting]
[boy 1] Get up, fat-ass.
So, asshole…
I told you to create ten accounts for me.
But you haven't done it yet.
Seong-jun, I'm sorry.
I'll make them right now.
It'll be really fast.
[sighs]
I told you to buy this,
and it's still for sale.
I'll work really hard. I promise.
[inhales sharply] We'll do our best.
- [boy 1] Let's get out of here.
- [boy 3] God damn, you guys are losers.
[boy 5] If you don't do your job,
we'll pay your mom's restaurant a visit.
- [boy 6] You stink of her side dishes.
- [boy 3] Yeah, you stink.
- [Seong-jun] You're in my way.
- [boy 3] Move it, pig.
- [boy 6] Let's leave these lovers alone.
- [Seong-jun] Good luck, fuckface.
[panting]
[both groaning]
I'm sorry, Gyu-Jin.
I'll try to run faster next time.
Take this for the blood.
Thanks.
I hate those assholes.
Be quiet.
Otherwise, they might come back.
[exhales] I can't breathe.
[music fades]
[sighs deeply]
I can't fucking breathe
with this thing on.
[woman 1] That's him, right?
He's so ashamed,
he has to keep his face covered.
[woman 2] You're right.
Why does someone like that
have to live in our neighborhood?
I don't feel safe anymore.
[women gasp]
[woman 3 humming innocently]
[Won-seong] Fucking bitches.
[bottles clink]
Hey, give me two packs of Marlboro Red.
[clerk] You'll have to remove your mask
and show me your ID.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Do I look like a high schooler to you?
No, uh, it's just store policy.
Just give me
the fucking cigarettes already.
- Uh--
- I haven't done anything wrong.
- I just came here to buy stuff.
- Um…
Why the fuck are you all looking at me
like I did something wrong?
[sighs]
I could kill everyone in that place.
[laughs]
[grunts]
Son of a bitch!
Why all the packages?!
You can't block the way
to someone's house!
If you ordered shit,
you should take them in
as soon as they arrive!
Who the fuck are these addressed to?
Park Kyeong-ja.
[Ji-yeong] Is this
Park Kyeong-ja's residence?
[Won-seong] My mom went to get groceries.
Come in.
Oh, okay.
This is for your mother.
Like me to bring it in?
Nah, it's fine, you know, I…
Please come in.
[uneasy music playing]
Holy shit. The fuck?
You can't be fucking serious.
This is crazy.
Oh!
They sent both a K1 and K2.
[chuckling]
[gun parts clicking]
[uneasy music continues]
[music intensifies]
[gun clicks]
[music fades]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughing, hollering]
Go! [groans]
[man 1] Hey. Move. Move.
- [man 2] Oh, this is gonna be fun.
- [man 3] Great.
- [man 4] Well, hello there.
- [captive] Jeong-man!
[man 1 laughing]
Please! You have to listen to me!
Jeong-man!
You can't do this.
[men laughing]
Please!
[sighs] First of all,
stop calling out my name.
Save your last breaths.
I've got a job to do.
I know. You're really good at your job.
Everyone knows how smart you are. Hmm?
[whimpers] With your brains,
you could do so much better
than being Seok-ho's muscle.
Seok-ho said he'd hand over his business.
All you have to do
is get rid of me, right?
But he's handing his business
over to Yong-gu.
It's what I heard him say.
He's never gonna let you be the boss!
Mr. Kim,
are you trying to hurt my feelings?
- [man 5] Hurry up and bury him! Come on!
- [man 3] Let's do this!
[man 5] We need to get out of here
before sunrise. Get a move on!
[captive] We've known each other
ten years!
Don't worry, we promise to hold
a nice funeral in your honor.
Let me live, and I'll give you
a useful piece of information!
[man 6] Bastards in your shoes
would say anything to live.
Listen!
It's not too late!
- You can take over everything! Jeong-man!
- [unsettling music playing]
- I swear, I can get you a gun!
- [man 3] Shut him up!
You want one, it's yours.
A gun in your hand by tomorrow!
- [man 3] Oh boy… [laughs]
- [captive] Jeong-man!
Please!
[eerie music playing]
Don't listen to him.
Let's just bury him and be done with it.
If the boss finds out
Mr. Kim is still alive, we're all fucked.
You have to believe me. Huh?
You can take over the whole thing.
[man 5] Come on. A gun?
You have to be out of your mind.
- [sighs]
- Let's get this over with, huh?
- Listen to me. I wouldn't lie about this.
- [man 5] Fine, let's say we get a gun.
What are we supposed to do,
just walk right in there
with a single gun?
- You know how many people work there?
- [Kim] Not just one gun! A hundred!
More than a hundred. Way more.
- A massive amount.
- [man 5] Shut up!
- Do you think we're a bunch of idiots?
- [phone buzzing]
- Give me a second.
- [man 5 sighs] Come on, man.
- [Kim] What's your name?
- [man 7] None of your business.
- Sir.
- [Seok-ho] Why haven't you reported back?
Don't hurt me!
Oh, I was just about to call you.
We're just finishing up.
- Sir…
- Yeah?
About the business you promised me
once this job was done…
Promise?
Oh, that. Listen, I'm busy right now.
- We'll talk.
- [line disconnects]
[Kim] He didn't answer you, did he?
I told you I'm not a liar.
[laughs]
Son of a bitch.
[metallic scraping]
Jeong-man! Jeong-man! Jeong-man, no!
[man 2 laughing] Oh-ho-ho-ho! Yeah!
Well, what are you waiting for?
Let's bury him.
[man 2] Yeah!
[man 5] Hurry this up. I'm freezing here.
Put him in.
[man 8] I wanna eat something first.
[music fades]
[breathing heavily]
[phone buzzing]
Ah shit! Why can't you leave me alone?
What do you want?
[man] This is your probation officer.
Where are you now?
Oh, fuck off.
You monitor me 24 hours a day.
it's not like you don't know where I am.
Exactly. Why are you
somewhere you don't usually frequent?
Why are you up that mountain?
I came here to get some fresh air.
Is that a crime?
You people are always suffocating me.
Hey.
Let me ask you a question.
Where the hell are you guys
monitoring me from anyway? Huh?
Tell me, where are you hiding?
I can't share that information.
Oh, you can't share that information?
I'm done talking to you, jackass!
[scoffs]
WARNING
THIS IS A MILITARY OPERATION ZONE
UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
AND PHOTOGRAPHY PROHIBITED
[man] Marksmen! On my order,
get ready to fire!
[distant gunfire]
[distant gunfire continues]
[unsettling music playing]
[laughing]
I haven't lost my touch at all.
[man] Prepare to fire!
Marksmen! When you're ready, fire!
[distant automatic gunfire]
[laughing manically]
- [laughter echoing]
- [music fades]
[keyboard clacking]
- I admire you, Officer Lee.
- [gasps]
[sighs deeply]
[sighs]
Uh, the list of reported firearms
I asked you for…
Here you go.
- [officer] Lee.
- Yes?
Did you request a list of items
cleared by customs? Here.
Yes, there's something that's bugging me.
I just wanted to check it out.
I mean,
it's good to see you working so hard,
but maybe let
the detectives do the sleuthing?
We shouldn't be stepping on any toes.
I won't be. No need to worry.
All right, I'll leave you to it.
- [Do] Thanks again.
- [officer] Sure.
CUSTOMS CLEARANCE LIST
FIREARMS
How come you haven't been
answering your phone? Huh?
And why are you so late?
Well, it took longer than expected
to wrap everything up.
You should've called earlier
to let me know.
- I hate waiting.
- Here's the picture of Mr. Kim.
Whoa, shit!
That's one hell of a photo you took.
[Seok-ho chuckling]
Wow.
You've got some talent.
Maybe you missed your calling, huh?
[chuckling]
Here.
- [man 1] The food here is good.
- [man 2] That means you're buying?
- Get out of here, you.
- Jeez.
[exhales nervously]
- Jeong-man.
- Yeah?
It's nice here, isn't it?
- Yes, sir.
- [chuckling]
So does that mean
that me and my boys
get to run this place from now on,
seeing as the job is over?
What the hell are you on about? [scoffs]
Yong-gu's going to manage this place.
[Seok-ho chuckles]
- What?
- You're not ready for that yet.
[man 1] Come on, man, trust me.
This is legit information.
[man 2] Sounds too good to be true.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ah, fuck me!
[breathing nervously]
What?
Well, you promised me last time we spoke
that you'd let us run
one of your businesses for you.
[laughing]
Listen to me.
This here is money.
Your kind don't fit here, you see?
[sighs]
The thing is,
my boys and I,
you don't know how hard we worked.
We killed for you.
Anything you asked, we would do.
- You can always rely on us--
- Cut the shit.
Okay? You're mine.
Just give us a chance to live like humans.
"Humans"? [scoffs]
What have you been all this time, then?
[chuckles softly]
Haven't we always just been
your obedient mutts?
[tense music playing]
"Mutts"?
Is that what you think you are?
Ah! Fucking shit!
Why do you have to be so serious?
You're making me feel so bad now.
Fine, all right?
Let's see how I can make this up
to you guys another day.
Just don't be an asshole.
Okay?
I… I have one last question.
Do you happen to know
the name of any of my boys?
Why? Is there someone in the group
you think I should know?
It's only because
they're all working so hard for you.
It would mean a lot
if you at least refer to them by name.
[Seok-ho] All right. Here.
Take this, and go get some food.
All of you eat,
and maybe take a goddamn bath.
You stink like shit.
Very kind, sir.
Hey! Hey. Toss that on your way out.
PRESIDENT KIM DEOK-HYEON
Don't want his ghost haunting me.
- [man 1] Does this hurt?
- Ow! Of course it hurts!
- Hey, cut it out! I told you it hurts.
- [man 1] Baby. I hardly touched you.
[man 3] He's here! He's here!
[man 4] Bravo!
Jeong-man, are we ready
to move into this place or what?
- [man 5] Let's party!
- [laughter]
Hold on. What's this?
You don't look happy.
[Jeong-man] Yong-gu
and his boys are in charge from now on.
I should've known
you'd backstab us, Seok-ho!
- For real? How?
- U-tae.
- You search inside?
- There's a storage room.
I couldn't get in.
Hey, Kim almost shit his pants
going into that hole.
What if he just fed us
a bunch of bullshit?
I don't wanna start all over again.
- Chang-ju.
- Yeah?
Take the others
to that gosiwon on the news.
See if there's anything salvageable.
You, come with me.
- [man 3 groans]
- Hey! Hey, hey.
- You heard the man.
- [Jeong-man] Guys.
[suspenseful music playing]
Take this and get cleaned up,
and get some good food.
I'm sorry things turned out
the way they did.
[Chang-ju] It's all right.
- Don't worry.
- [Jeong-man] See you guys later.
- Hey, wait up.
- [man 4] Let's go.
Hey, what's gotten into you?
What is it, hmm?
Come on, enough with the secrets. Jeong!
- You know where Mr. Kim's car is?
- Yeah. Why?
Let's check it.
[engine starts]
[music fades]
[distant sirens wailing]
[phone buzzes]
[Seong-jun] Fuck-gyu.
Get your mom's ID and get over here now.
- [woman 1] Enjoy.
- [man 1] The rolled omelet?
Of course. One rolled omelet, please!
[man 2] Dessert is on me.
DAESEONG RESTAURANT
- [woman 2] Thank you.
- [man 2] I'm glad…
- [woman 2] That's too bad
- [woman 1] Oh!
Hi.
[woman 1 chuckles softly]
What's wrong?
You look so nervous, sweetie.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
Could I borrow some money?
How much money?
[inhales sharply]
Why do you suddenly need money?
Is something going on?
No, um, I just need money.
Really, I'm fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes, I'm more than okay.
Forget it.
[woman 1] You're a good boy. It's fine.
I'm busy,
so grab whatever you need from my wallet.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
HONG, SEO-JEONG
- [woman 2] Thanks for the food, ma'am!
- [Seo-jeong] See you soon!
- I'm gonna get going.
- Oh! Okay.
[door opens, closes]
- [muffled upbeat music playing]
- [boys chattering, laughing]
[boy 1] Hey, here comes Gyu!
- [indistinct chatter]
- [upbeat music continues]
- [boy 2] You got it.
- [boy 3] Got it.
[boy 2] Yeah!
[Seong-jun] Did you bring what I asked?
- [upbeat music continues]
- [boys singing karaoke]
[boy 4] Hey!
[music stops]
So Fuck-gyu wants to die.
You wanna die?
Uh, well, actually…
[microphone feedback rings]
[unsettling music playing]
- [grunting]
- [Seong-jun] Am I a joke to you?
I mean, I couldn't get my mom's ID, so…
Then steal the whole fucking wallet!
[breathing anxiously]
I… I… I really…
I'm very sorry…
But you're gonna use the ID to borrow
money from a loan shark. Right?
My mom, she works so hard.
What if I just tried to make
the photos racier?
[grunts]
Do you honestly think I give a fuck
how hard your mom works?
Okay…
I don't give a shit.
I know.
[Seong-jun] So let's try again.
Can you bring her ID to me tomorrow?
[splutters]
Is that a yes or a no?
I, uh…
- [groans]
- Yes or no, you fucking loser?
Um… I don't know.
Don't make me angry!
Time to fuck you up.
[Gyu-jin grunting, groaning]
[boy 2] Loser! Nothing but a mama's boy.
- [music fades]
- [tires screech]
[U-tae] We gotta find the keys!
- The keys!
- [Jeong-man] Check the tires!
Look for them!
[sighs angrily] Where the fuck are they?
Found them!
I got 'em, I got 'em, I got 'em!
Open it.
Move!
[U-tae breathing nervously]
[tense music playing]
[U-tae] Oh… Holy shit!
No!
Jeong-man!
We… we should think about this.
You can't be rash!
No! How stupid does this make us, huh?
What are we going to do with one gun?
If things go wrong,
the two of us are seriously fucked!
Okay, then what?
You wanna keep waiting for scraps?
- [exhales sharply]
- U-tae.
That prick will never let us grow.
Do what you're told, have more patience…
It's just… That should be my business!
[exhales forcefully]
You, us,
all our boys.
That bastard's dangling a treat
with no intention of giving it.
Wanna be a gofer forever?
- F… fuck.
- Living like this?
[lock clicks]
U-tae.
I see this…
as an opportunity.
[breathing deeply]
[tense music continues]
[music fades]
[Do] Where did you get the gun?
It was couriered to me.
Why would a stranger send you
a package with a gun in it by courier?
The truth.
[intriguing music playing]
Ever received a package
from an unknown sender?
I don't know.
[Do] Around what time
does the courier come?
[man 1] Between 2:00 and 4:00 p.m.
YEONGSEONG GOSIWON
- [Do] Seen this man around here?
- [man 2] Uh, no.
[Do] Which day of the week
does the recycling get picked up?
[woman] Tuesdays and Thursdays.
- [man 1] Sure you looked up there?
- [man 2] There's nothing.
[man 3] I already checked.
[man 4] Where the hell is it?
Seriously, are we sure he wasn't lying?
[man 1] No, he said it was here.
Wait, hold on.
This…
No, this isn't it. Jesus!
- [man 4] Hey--
- [Do] This is the police.
What are you doing here?
[man 1] Uh,
we were gonna make some cash
selling boxes.
- Got a problem with that?
- [man 5] Here we go.
- [men chuckling]
- [Do] Didn't you see the tape back there?
This is a crime scene.
You can't just come in here.
- [man 1] I don't know how to read.
- [man 2] Dumbass.
Our mistake, Officer.
[phone buzzing]
Yes, Captain?
So you know
all that stuff the kid told us?
I don't think we have to worry about it.
It was all lies.
What?
We ran the records
of all the courier companies,
and there's no record of anything
being sent to his address.
In fact, he hasn't received
a single package in the last three years.
He keeps saying all this weird stuff
about how everyone's got a trigger
in their hearts, or some crazy shit.
None of it is useful.
Anyway, we'll recheck the security cams
and the nearby vehicles
and I'll let you know if we find anything.
[sighs] Thank you, sir.
Anything else,
you can just give me a call.
I appreciate all your support.
Okay, thanks. Have a good one.
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[car horn honking]
NAME: JEON WON-SEONG
[Seo] 23S-249.
That's Won-seong's car, right?
- [officer 1] Get in closer.
- What's going on?
[Do] Jeong-tae did receive a package.
I saw the box.
And I think a man named Won-seong
got the same package.
Won-seong?
He's the guy we're chasing right now.
Hold on. We've almost caught up to him.
Call you when we're there.
Okay. Whoa, whoa!
[sirens wailing]
- Go.
- [officer 2] Yes, sir!
- [officer 3] Won-seong, out of the car!
- [officer 4] Hands up!
[officer 3] Raise your hands!
Get out of the car! Now!
- Whoa!
- Move out of the way!
What's wrong? Why are you stopping me?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Wait.
Sir, do you know this person?
We're looking for this suspect.
He… got off a while back.
Detective!
We found Won-seong's ankle bracelet
and cell phone.
[tense music continues]
[music fades]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
- [creaking]
- [music fades]
[creaking]
[dramatic music playing]
[music fades]
- Who are you?
- [grunts] That hurts!
Wait!
- [sweeping music playing]
- My name's Moon Baek.
Moon Baek!
What are you doing here?
[groans] I-- I…
I came to pick something up.
A… a package.
[funky rock music playing]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]